The Racket is a crime, drama film directed by Lewis Milestone.
A renegade police captain sets out to catch a sadistic mob boss.
Preserved by the Academy Film Archive in 2016.
Police Captain James McQuigg, played by Thomas Meighan.
Nick Scarsi, played by Louis Wolheim.
Helen Hayes, played by Marie Prevost.
Patrolman Johnson, played by G. Pat Collins.
Spike Corcoran, played by Henry Sedley.
Joe Scarsi, played by George E. Stone.
The Racket is a 1928 American silent crime drama film directed by Lewis Milestone and
starring Thomas Meighan, Marie Prevost, Louis Wolheim, and George E.
The film was produced by Howard Hughes, written by Bartlett Cormack and
Tom Miranda, and was distributed by Paramount Pictures.
It was adapted from Cormack's 1927 Broadway play The Racket.
The film explores themes of bootlegger, reporter, silent film.
The tone is emotional.